Contact

Lisbon 00447760660485 (Mobile) sergiofpc2015@yahoo.es

www.linkedin.com/in/sergio-constantino-58511314 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Food & Beverage

Languages

Microsoft Office

German (Elementary)
Portuguese (Native or Bilingual)
Spanish (Full Professional)

Sergio Constantino

Head Waiter, Chef de Rang /Steward/Hotels/Ocean and River Cruises, Freelancer Recruiter, , Bartender, Writer Lisbon Area, Portugal

Summary

Experience Head Waiter / Waiter, steward organized, reliable, self motivated, hard worker, perfect eye for details, always with a smile on service, bilinguale, very organized. Dedicated, fast, funny, napkin folder skills, organization skills. Buffet and table decoration skills, fluent in English. Spanish, Portuguese,

Human and public relation skills.

Independent partner of Incruises.

Caviar suplier

Experience in Mirrow services, Ghost services, American services, French services, Russian services, Butler service.

Email: sergiofpc2015@yahoo.es

Cooking skills, i have experience working in luxury ocean cruises, river cruises, ferry boats, luxury 5 star hotels in Portugal, England, Spain, Austria since 1991, working in restaurans, hospitality it is my passion, i just love it. Ocean cruises and river cruises jobs review: Royal Caribbean cruise line 1991, Premier cruise line, 1996, Pullmantur cruises 2002, Azamara cruises 2005, Silver Sea cruises 2006, Princess cruises 2007 and working as well in my first book project launched in the same year (Nautical Jobs Hunter-cruise career guide by Sergio Constantino, Cunard cruise line (White star academy) 2011, Avalon river cruises 2014, Scylla river cruises 2017, Scenic river cruises 2018.

River Chefs 2019

Between the years of working at sea i had the experience of working in some 5 star luxury hotels in Portugal, Spain, England and Austria. i have Swiss national insurance number, UK national insurance number, Spanish national insurance number amd Portuguese national insurance number.

I am looking for to keep going with my career with Swiss contracts or in UK in hospitality but i am free and available to receive any job propositions anywhere in the world.

Experience in. fine dining, silver service, mirrow service, ghost service, american service and others. decoration skills. buffet supervisor.

i also would love to get the opportunity to have HR recruiter trainings regarding my experience and passion of helping others to find and get jobs.

Caviar Suplier as well.

i will really apprecciate if any one can help me in this metter. kind regards

Sergio Constantino

Experience

Hampshire Hotels
Bartender/Chef de Rang/ Head Waiter
October 2019 - March 2020 (6 months)

Passenger delivery restaurant profissional services, hotel services, silver service, mirrow service, ghost service, american service,

Scenic River Cruises & RIVER Advice Chef de Rang January 2019 - October 2019 (10 months) Swizerland

Waiter 2 season, Scenic river cruises

Scenic river cruises
Chef de Rang
April 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 7 months)

Scylla river cruises, Edelweiss Gastro Chef de Rang March 2017 - December 2017 (10 months)

Germany

Hotel Alpenrose GmbH Head Waiter February 2015 - January 2016 (1 year)

Melchseefrutt Switzerland

Avalon River Cruises
Chef de Rang
March 2014 - January 2015 (11 months)

Quay Lagos Head Waiter February 2013 - December 2013 (11 months) Algarve south Portugal

I am a experienced Waiter, Head Waiter, Steward, i am looking for a new job in a luxury hotel, Cruise Ship, privat yacht or ferry right this moment, if anyone as any information or knowns about a position available, please contact me

Robinson Club Hotels Head Waiter September 2011 - December 2012 (1 year 4 months) Zurs Austria

Cunard Line Chef de Rang - White Star Academy March 2011 - September 2011 (7 months) Pacific ocean

Chef de Rang in MS Queen Victoria

Waiter (Chef de Rang)

Silver Sea Cruises Chef de Rang January 2008 - November 2009 (1 year 11 months) Mediterranean Sea- Ship Silver Sea Cloud

Chewton Glen 5 Star Hotel Chef de Rang January 2007 - December 2007 (1 year) New Milton, Hampshire, Reino Unido Princess Cruises
Waiter and Buffet Supervisor
January 2006 - December 2006 (1 year)
Ship Grand Princess&Caribbean Princess

Azamara Club cruises
Waiter ship Azamara Quest
March 2004 - August 2005 (1 year 6 months)
Caribbean sea-Ship Azamara Quest

Pullmantur Cruises
Waiter/ Captain Waiter
January 2002 - January 2004 (2 years 1 month)
Ship Oceanic & Ship RFive Blue Dream

P&O Ferries Steward January 2001 - November 2001 (11 months) Hull, Roterdam-Ship Pride of Hull

Royal Caribbean cruise line Assistant Waiter ship Nordic Prince January 1991 - June 1991 (6 months) Alaska

Education

Escola de hotelaria e turismo de Faro EHTA Restaurante e Bar Course, Restaurante e Bar · (1990 - 1991)

IN LOCO STUDIES - FARO - PORTUGAL